startthedownload.com 2017-10-07

# Privacy Policy - startthedownload.com

### Overview of Our Privacy Policy

We supply free entertainment and utility software including video playing software, password managers, file zipping software and games. Our Products include Toolbars. Our Toolbars add search functionality to your browser. They also allow one click access to news and our offers. (We refer to our software and Products throughout this agreement as our “Services”).

We offer our Services to you in exchange for your agreement to view promotions, advertisements, or participate in other offers. We also offer you the opportunity to download third-party software.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand our online privacy practices regarding:

  * Information we collect
  * How we use the information
  * How we share your information, if at all
  * Your choices

We may make available shorter versions of this Privacy Policy. We also may supplement this policy for specific Services. Where there is a conflict between this policy and our summary this policy will govern. Where there is a conflict between this policy and our supplement, the supplement will govern.

We may change this privacy policy. If we change this policy we will post the changes to this privacy statement, our websites’ homepages, and other places we deem appropriate. We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

## Some Terms We Use in This Policy

Offers include promotions, advertisements contests and third-party software presented by our Partners and us.

Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is any information that identifies or could be used to identify, contact or locate you. It also includes your credit card number.

Partner is an advertiser, or other entity with whom we have a business relationship to provide Offers.

Service includes, but is not limited to, our screensaver, wallpaper, game, animated gif, clip art, buddy icon, greeting card, browser skin, font, desktop theme, html editor, sound effect, social networking, storage, and calendar software, as well as our Toolbars.

Subsidiary is an entity wholly owned or related to testingwarehouse.net.

User means an individual that has accessed the Sites on which we host our Products or Services.

We and Our refer to testingwarehouse.net and its subsidiaries.

You and Your refer to each user and his or her agents.

### Personal Information We Collect

We may collect personal information from you when you use our site, navigate around our site, or use our services. Your participation is voluntary and you have the choice not to disclose any information that we request.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strike to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolutely security.

## Installation

During installation, we will present you with Offers. You may choose not to accept our Offers. Your participation is voluntary, you are not required to disclose to our Partners any information they request. However, if you provide your Personally Identifiable Information in response to any Offer, we will share it with our Partners so they can provide you with the Offers in which you have expressed interest.

## Contacts/IP Information

If you voluntarily submit information or contact us (e.g. password request, technical support), we may keep a record of this communication. We do not merge this information with your Personally Identifiable Information.

## Aggregate Information We Collect

When you use our Services, we may collect tracking information such as your IP address, browser type, the type of operating system you use, details about your computer hardware, the applications you have installed on your PC, the domain name of your Internet service provider, and pages you visited on our Sites. None of the information identifies you personally and we do not link aggregate information to Personally Identifiable Information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small text file sent to your browser. Cookies are stored on your computer’s hard drive for record keeping purposes. We and our Partners use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once you close your browser, the cookie will terminate. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s help file.

We use cookies to: 1) Remind us of who you are and to access your account information (stored on our computers). We also use cookies to store your zip code and other information you have submitted for other services, such as displaying your local weather. We do not store Personally Identifiable Information in our cookies and we do not tie the information in our cookies to our customers’ Personally Identifiable Information

Some of the Partner Offers on our Services may also use cookies. We have no control over our partners’ privacy policies. We also have no control over their cookies, the information collected and its use.

We may use Cookies to provide a targeted advertising experience on and off our site.

## Web beacons or Pixels

We and our Partners employ a software technology that helps us better manage content on our site. Web beacons or Pixels are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. They track your online Web movement. We embed Pixels invisibly on Web pages. They are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by Pixels to our customers’ Personally Identifiable Information.

Some of the Partner Offers may also use Pixels. We have no control over our partners’ Pixels. We also have no control over how they use information collected.

## Software Information

We employ a technology that allows us to determine the operating systems you are using and to view your computer’s registry. Software installed on your computer has unique registry keys. By viewing your registry, we are able to detect whether you have a compatible operating system, compatible versions of DirectX, and Flash Player installed. We use your registry information to determine whether our software offers are compatible with software already present on your PC. We do not tie registry information gathered to our customers’ Personally Identifiable Information.

## Hardware Information

Your computer’s operating system also stores hardware information that we examine to determine your computer’s hardware configuration including the amount of memory and the type of video card your computer has, as well as the speed of your processor. We use the information to determine whether our software offers are compatible with your computer hardware. We do not tie hardware information to our customers’ Personally Identifiable Information.

We also collect additional aggregate information when you install our Toolbars.

### How We Use Your Information?

We only use information as it is needed for each specific visit. We do not use your PII in any way at this point. We may also use this information to provide targeted advertisements.

## Third Parties and Advertising

Third parties advertise on our Sites, and we also contract with third parties to serve ads across the Internet. These third parties may serve ads about our products or services, or third party products or services in which, based on your Session Data, we or our business partners believe you may be interested. These third parties may seek to use cookies and pixel tags, including those collected on our Site, to track Session Data about the ads you have seen and types of things in which you appear interested. These third parties may also use combined information about your visits to our Site and other sites in order to provide advertisements about related goods and services that may be of interest to you. You can opt-out of the third party advertising program by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative website http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp. Opting out of a network does not mean you will no longer receive online advertising. It does mean that the network from which you opted out will no longer deliver ads tailored to your Web preferences and usage patterns.

When you click on a third party advertisers’ link from our Site, you will enter the third party’s site. We are not responsible for such third party’s sites. You should carefully review the privacy statements of any other site you visit, because those privacy statements will apply to your visit to that site, and may be very different from our policy.

## Multi-site Advertising

We have online Behavorial Advertising on our Site.

Advertisers and advertising networks use tracking technologies to collect information about users’ computers or mobile devices and their online activities (for example, web pages visited and searches made) as well as general geographic location and use that information to display targeted ads to users. We sometimes allow these ad companies to collect such information when you use our sites and apps to enable them to display targeted ads to you on and off our Site.

Many ad companies are members of the Network Advertising Initiative. NAI members allow users to opt out of being tracked by cookies. To opt out of cookie tracking by NAI members, you may visithttp://www.networkadvertising.org/ and click on the “Consumer Opt-out” button. Companies may also be members of the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) and to opt out of cookie tracking by DAA members, you may visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.

### How We Share Your Information?

Partners may sponsor Offers or we may co-sponsor an Offer with a Partner through the software. You should always assume data collected when you fill-in an Offer will be shared with a Partner. If an Offer requires you to leave our websites, you should know that our Partners may collect Personally Identifiable Information about you. We do not control these Partner sites. This Privacy Policy does not cover our partners’ websites and information practices. Once you have voluntarily submitted information to our Partners, your personal information is subject to their privacy policy. We have no liability or responsibility for these privacy policies or the use of any Personally Identifiable Information transferred to Partners.

If you no longer wish to be contacted by our partners you must contact that partner directly to opt-out.

Our Partners change from time to time, and therefore it is not possible to provide an exhaustive list. We strive to select trustworthy Partners who offer high quality products or services of interest to you. If you are unhappy with one of our Partners, tell us by e-mailing us at support@startthedownload.com.

We may periodically use third parties to meet your needs. For example if you buy a game from us that may be handled by Real.com or one of our other game partners. If we hire a third-party service provider, they will be prohibited from using your Personally Identifiable Information for any purpose not enumerated in this section.

The following describes some of the ways that we may disclose your information to our Partners:

## Search Partners

We may transmit your search queries (made on the Site or within one of our Software Offers) to search Partners, who use this information to provide us with search results, which we then will display to you.

## Third-Party Advertisements and Software

When you request or submit your information online to a Partner in response to any Offer, we transfer your information for each request made to that Partner.

## Our Products

We do not require you to provide Personally Identifiable Information during the installation process of our Toolbars of other software products. However, when you use these Software Offers to access Download Offers (e.g. games) you may be required to provide Personally Identifiable Information. In addition, we will show you Offers during the installation process.

## Sale, Merger or Asset Transfer

We may buy other businesses or their assets or sell our business assets. Customer information is generally one of the business assets involved in such transactions. Thus, in the event that we or all of our assets are acquired, customer information, including any information collected through the Sites or the Services would be one of the transferred assets.

From time to time we use third-parties when providing Services to you. We will only share information with third-parties necessary for them to provide the Services you have requested. Third-parties are prohibited from using your Personally Identifiable Information for promotional purposes.

### Your Choices

## Cookies

By modifying your browser preferences, you can choose to, accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or you can reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies, you may be unable to use our Services.

## Modifications

For any of our sites you may edit your account information and user profile by using your username and password.

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you want your information deleted from our systems you should email our customer support team as support@startthedownload.com.

## Security and Passwords

We cannot and do not ensure or warrant the security of any information collected, transmitted over the Internet, or maintained in your user profile. You agree that any data transmission you make or receive through the Site or the Service is at your own risk.

No method of transmitting or storing electronic data is ever completely secure, and therefore we cannot warrant or guarantee that such information will never be accessed, used, or released in a manner that is inconsistent with this policy.

We do not knowingly collect information about children under the age of 13. We encourage parents and guardians to be familiar with the web sites that their children visit the Federal Trade Commission (“FTC”) regulates the means by which web site operators collect and use personal information from children under 13, pursuant to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (the “Act”). For more information about the Act and children’s on-line privacy in general, visit the FTC’s web site at www.ftc.gov/privacy. For safety tips on privacy visit www.OnGuardOnline.gov.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Miscellaneous Provisions

YOUR USE OF OUR SERVICES IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. OUR SERVICES (INCLUDING ALL CONTENT AND FUNCTIONS MADE AVAILABLE ON OR ACCESSED THROUGH OUR SITES) IS PROVIDED “AS IS.” WE MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER ABOUT: (1) THE ACCURACY, MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT; (2) THE SERVER THAT MAKES THE SERVICES AVAILABLE, INCLUDING THAT IT IS FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER COMPONENTS THAT MAY INFECT, HARM, OR CAUSE DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER EQUIPMENT OR ANY OTHER PROPERTY WHEN YOU ACCESS, BROWSE, DOWNLOAD FROM, OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITE.

UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO OUR NEGLIGENCE, SHALL WE BE LIABLE FOR ANY CONSEQUENTIAL, DIRECT, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR SPECIAL DAMAGES RELATED TO (A) THE USE OF, (B) THE INABILITY TO USE, OR (C) ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN THE CONTENTS AND FUNCTIONS OF OUR SITES AND SERVICES, EVEN IF WE OR OUR REPRESENTATIVES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN NO EVENT SHALL OUR TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ALL DAMAGES, LOSSES, AND CAUSES OF ACTION (WHETHER IN CONTRACT OR TORT, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) EXCEED $10.00.

## Indemnification

You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold us and all of our agents, directors, employees, information providers, licensors and licensees, officers, and subsidiaries (collectively, “Indemnified Parties”) harmless from and against any and all liability and costs (including, without limitation, attorneys’ fees and costs) incurred by you in connection with any claim arising out of any breach by you of this Privacy Policy. You will cooperate as fully as reasonably required in our defense of any claim. We reserve the right, at our own expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you and you shall not in any event settle any matter without our written consent.

## International Policy

Our Services are hosted by servers in the United States. Accordingly, if you are located outside of the United States, we will transfer the personal information you provide to us to the United States. By submitting your personal information, you fully understand and consent, to its transfer, storage and processing in the United States.

## Enforcement / Redress

If you feel that we have not followed our Privacy policy, please let us know. Also, if you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy policy, its implementation, or would like a written copy, please feel free to contact us at:

#### startthedownload.com

Alternatively, if you would like, contact us via e-mail at support@startthedownload.com.

Last modified on **March 10, 2017.**
